nextgenlinks.com 2010-09-01

# NextGen Links - Privacy Policy. Link Exchanges, Linking, Link Exchange Service and Link Partnerships.

| 

Our Firm Commitment To Privacy

 ** **Next** **Gen**** _links_ has created this statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following statement discloses all of our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

**USER / CUSTOMER DEFINITIONS:**  
"User" means any person who establishes or accesses connection to ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. "Customer" or "Member" means any person gaining additional or paid access to products & services provided by ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. 

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY:**  
****Next** **Gen**** _links_ is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13; nor do we target our web sites, products and/or services to children under the age of 13. 

**THIRD PARTIES:**  
We have never shared our customers' names with third parties; unless, a user has specifically requested to receive special offers or promotions with an advertiser found on our web site; or, if a user creates a public profile specifically for the purpose of being shared within an online community hosted or owned by ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. Customer information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without the consent of the customer, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested by the customer. We value your business and we respect your privacy. 

**NO SPYWARE / NO ADWARE:**  
None of the software available from ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ contains any form of spyware or adware. Software from third parties that ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ may sometimes provide links for, is not within the control of ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. Therefore, third party software, may or may not contain forms of adware or spyware. We ask that you carefully read all license agreements related to any software product that you intend to download. 

**DATA COLLECTED:**  
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. In addition, we use cookies and 1x1 pixels. Cookies and 1x1 pixels are used to deliver better services, provide account management, and targeted marketing messages to you, the web surfer. These tools are used to collect anonymous data, and in some instances where personally-identifiable information has been provided by a user; to provide account services, and/or to provide better/more relevant messages to that user. 

**REGISTRATION FORMS:**  
Our site registration forms require our users to enter their email address, contact info, and sometimes personally identifiable information such as: email address, first name, last name, address, city, state, phone, date of birth, and postal/zip code. We use data provided through registration form(s) to send the user information about our company, create online community profiles, and to provide (or sell) various subscription services and/or other products. 

**NETWORK SECURITY:**  
****Next** **Gen**** _links_ has put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard the information that is collected. Various security technologies have been implemented to ensure that external parties cannot access or modify Users' personal information on the ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ Network. Specifically, Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption is used on specific Web pages to safeguard online purchase transactions. SSL technology is the industry standard protocol for secure, Web-based communications. 

**INFORMATION SAFEGUARDS:**  
We use appropriate security safeguards and encryptions to protect your information. We use (custom) high level encryption methods on passwords and personal security questions, as well as other applicable security measures, such as SSL ( Secure Socket Layer Encryption ) to prevent any inappropriate entity or individual from gaining access to or knowledge of any data you decide to provide us with. 

**FINANCIAL INFORMATION:**  
Customer payment information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) are all processed securely through the PayPal® service. ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ does not store any Customer financial information on it's own servers, OR in it's own databases; regardless of whether you enter your financial information at ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ or directly through PayPal®. For more information about PayPal® and their privacy policies, please visit: ( www.paypal.com ). 

**LIABILITY:**  
Our sites contain links and advertisements for various other sites. ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. In addition, ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ offers services that provide access to online communities hosted by ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. If you provide information for a public profile that is shared within one or all of these communities, ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ will not be held responsible for how this information is used by others who view such profiles. 

**COOKIES:**  
****Next** **Gen**** _links_ uses cookies to track whether or not visitors have seen or used our sites, products, and services. Cookies are also used for advertising and tracking of advertising campaigns. In some cases, cookies may be used to store account identification information, or customized user settings and preferences for sites belonging to ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. Some cookies may contain personally identifiable information. 

**ABUSE:**  
If someone abuses our system, we may disclose their IP address and any pertinent information we have about them to law enforcement agencies or other organizations involved in apprehending that person. In addition, ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ reserves to the right to work directly with law enforcement agencies that subpoena ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ for information related to any criminal investigation. 

**OPT-OUT:**  
You may opt-out of all the services, tools, products, and/or software that ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ provides at any time you wish. To opt-out of COOKIES, please disable COOKIES on your browser. To opt-out or delete all of your accounts, email, profiles, and/or other memberships or subscriptions associated with ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ ; please contact us in writing ( or via email ); with a request for termination of such services. 

**BACKUPS:**  
Daily backup information is stored on secure devices maintained by ****Next** **Gen**** _links_. If you decide to opt-out of any or all of the services offered by ****Next** **Gen**** _links_ ; any information that was deleted, may remain on backup for a period not to exceed 90 days. After 90 days, any and all information that is stored on backup will have been permanently deleted as well. 

**CONTACTING THE SITE:**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of our company, or your dealings with our company, you can contact support using: ( support@nextgenlinks.com ).

﻿  |
